<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code up North</title>
    <link>http://blog.skellcoder.com/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Code up North</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 20:28:24 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.skellcoder.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>So I started an blog.</title>
      <link>http://blog.skellcoder.com/post/2017_02_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 20:28:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skellcoder.com/post/2017_02_19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My blogging has never been my biggest strength.
The last blogging attempt was an whopping disaster, lasting for one post with maybe two-three sentence.
Hoping that this blog will be a bit more active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why should I have an blog? Since school I felt that I have stopped doing deep learning, with this blog I will try to
go trough subjects I feel that I want to learn in more detail. I will also do it in public so I can improve my writing and force me
to actually do the writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;Content?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will focus on programming and tech but may branch out. Topics I know I want to get a SOLID grip on is,
SOLID, Tensorflow, learning more languages (Erlang, GO, Haskell) and possibly do a couple of posts with focus on a couple of good books (Clean code/r).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;blog-power&#34;&gt;Blog power&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blog is powered with &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;hugo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wercker.com/&#34;&gt;wercker&lt;/a&gt; and deployed on github pages.
My first thought was doing it with something simple like wordpress or medium. But then I found hugo a simple
static site generator built with GO. Don&amp;rsquo;t know if the best platform but I got a good vibe when I started to use it.
Still a few kinks to work out with the layout but probably somebody has already had that problem and asked on SO.
You can see the progress (or lack of) on my &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/skellcoder/skellcoder-blog&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>